Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Why don't we show them what you really are?
My magic is never giving up!
The Queen of Witches removed the limiter on Asta's anti-magic energy, awakening him to his true potential.
What's happening?
My body's chilled to the bone, like I'm floating in a freezing lake.
And my mind feels clearer than ever.
And my physical strength is overflowing!
I'd suspected you were of a certain bloodline.
But I was wrong.
Due to your body's mutation, the mana did not dwell within you.
Simply put, you're defective.
You're defective.
But because of that, you're able to hold the sword.
You aren't anything special.
Not in the slightest.
And that is precisely what makes you extraordinary.
Black meteorite!
Asta defeated Ladros with his newfound power, and Ladros turned over a new leaf.
But then...
Yes, my magic allows me to manipulate blood as I please.
So for as long as you live, you're going to carry this weapon as though it were mine.
The Queen of Witches revealed that she'd been after Asta's anti-magic ability from the start.
Taking control over his body.
And now for your first order.
I want you to kill every one of these weaklings with your own hands.
Then tell you about input cetera.
Then tell someone計fang from the spot where you believe it is,
Time to keep on saying it.
To bring it to the right of your own hands.
Thank you.
Asta, no!
Asta! Don't do this!
Wake up!
Now then, which one of them would I like to slaughter first?
Ah yes.
It's only proper to start with royalty.
Kill her!
Don't hurt her!
Hey, get a hold of yourself!
This isn't you, Asta!
No use. I can't get through to him.
It's me, Noelle! I know you remember!
Now this is justice.
How fitting to think that a Clover Kingdom royal would be vanquished by their blade.
You can't!
Asta!
Snap out of it!
No! Please stop!
It's time to say farewell.
Asta!
Don't listen to her!
Do it.
Curses.
He isn't even conscious.
Thank God.
So, despite all of that, she still doesn't have total control over him.
I won't die.
No matter what, I won't let you kill me!
Don't even try!
Once I get myself free, I can undo this stupid spell!
Like it's nothing!
Puppet's blood binds to the blood in his body, bending him to my will.
He can fight it, but he can never undo it.
A magicless neophyte like him cannot escape its hold.
Oh, stop!
Oh, dear.
So stubborn.
Don't do it!
Stop this!
I'll make you a deal!
Oh!
You let him go, and I'll stay here for good.
I will never disobey you again.
So please.
No.
He's going to kill each of them perfectly, here and now,
so that I can put an end to your defiance.
Vanessa, my scrying foretold that you would someday come back here alive with something I wanted.
That's why I didn't search for you.
However, I must admit I had not anticipated that this something I wanted would reveal itself to be a human boy wielding an anti-magic weapon.
What did you gain by fleeing from this forest?
You may have shared a fleeting bond with these imperfect worms, but in the end, it only led them to their deaths.
No matter where you run, your ties to me cannot be broken.
To you?
You are my daughter, after all, and family lasts forever.
We're family? What do you mean by that?
I'm saying that you belong to me.
No way!
I'm serious!
How?
I just remembered, there's a place in that village that has really good cake!
Cool! We should go check it out!
Hey, wait up! I want to go! Please stick me with you!
Don't leave me here alone! I need a way out!
Don't leave me here alone!
Vanessa!
Your Majesty! Can you please let me go? I'm sick of this place!
It's so lonely being trapped here! How long do I have to stay?
I'm begging you! I'm trying really hard, but I just don't think my thread magic has the kind of power you say it does! Can I go now?
No, I'm certain that you possess the ability to control destiny. My divinations have confirmed as much.
Yes, but...
How long I keep you here depends on you.
It's simple, really. Find a spell that controls destiny. At that time you may leave.
Remember, Vanessa, we are family.
If you're my family, then let me go!
Out of the question.
You belong to me, and I will choose your fate.
Your Majesty! Come back! Please get me out of this place! I don't want to be all by myself!
I told you, I can't do it.
I heard that cute little cake shop in the village ended up closing down for good.
That's too bad!
Hey, did you know?
There's a big town outside this forest, and I've heard there are tons of people living there who aren't witches!
Silly Vanessa! You must have told us about that place a thousand times now!
Well, isn't that where all the other witches have gone? To have fun and find boyfriends and stuff like that?
Why not escape this cage and join them? You want to, right?
What? No, that's impossible. I mean...
I could never defy the Queen of Witches.
Hey, it's alright. Don't look so sad.
I know. Want me to ask the Queen of Witches for you?
That won't work. You're nothing more than a doll I made using my magic.
So if I can't do something, you certainly can't either.
That's right. And this whole conversation is just you talking to yourself.
Someday, it would be nice to have real friends to talk to.
Yes, it would.
But it'll never happen.
I'm stuck here.
Inside this cage forever.
I'll never...
I'll never be free.
I wonder what all the chaos is about.
It's a man!
Intruder!
What did they say?
Geez, relax. I'm just doing some martial arts training.
Are they really gonna chase me out of here for being a man?
I've never seen one of them before.
I'll give that hysterical old hag one thing, though. She really knows how to fight.
Wait, is he saying he fought the queen?
Now then, where am I?
Uh, and what's your story? Why are you sitting in a birdcage?
Well, sir, I, uh... You see, this is my home. The queen of witches locked me in and I can't get out.
Like a bad bird. But you gotta go outside every once in a while, right?
I've never left the cage.
Not once. Sounds like a tough life. But hey, it's your lucky day. There's a hole in the wall now. You can sneak out.
Oh, thanks, but I can't run away from her majesty. I have to stay here. This cage is my fate.
Your fate? Really? You're saying you ended up here because it's your fate? Yeah, yeah. Old Mr. Fate, I know.
Man, I'm not a fan of that guy. Why would anyone obey him? I live how I want, even if it means kicking fate's ass.
But at the moment, I don't stand a chance in hell against that crazy old batter's got you trapped here.
Which means I probably ought to make a run for it while I can.
Hope it works out, little birdie.
Wait, don't go! What should I do now?
Well, that's up to you.
If I really am a bird in a cage, then I have wings like a bird, too. If I want to, I can fly away from all this.
It's my choice!
You wanted to know what I gained from the outside world.
Well, I learned something.
Which is?
You're not my family, and you never were.
Cause the Black Bulls are my family.
family and now i'm about to have them taken away from me right before my eyes
if i can't put a stop to this then what good am i to them
please if that power really does exist magic of mine change this face
what is that
incredible she's done it
at last the red thread of fate
in all these years i never imagined that it would look like this a cat
so she's discovered the spell she really can manipulate destiny in that case let's give it a
try
is that all it touched him but nothing seemed to happen
it's time to pay for underestimating the great queen of witches
it appears you are still imperfect but not to worry in my infinite perfection i shall see that you
receive proper training from this point forward
she lives impossible i was certain he'd slashed that girl in two it's time to pay for underestimating the
great queen of witches how strange did i not say the same thing moments ago
he missed this must be a mistake
it's over for you
don't hurt her
no this cannot be kill that one
her heart striking the cat directly
it dispelled puppet's blood
but my manipulation should have been unstoppable
i see this is the power that can control destiny
when someone is touched by that animal it would seem the spell takes over that person's fate
altering its course to work in the caster's advantage
vanessa must not be able to visualize an outcome in which her friends are killed
so she imagines scenarios where my attacks fail by a narrow margin
the cat is harmless and unstoppable well how about that
i'm impressed that you've realized this power
vanessa you've done so well how i've waited for this day blood magic
have it's blood
vanessa
now both you and your newfound ability will be mine to command as i please
it'll be the perfect enhancement to an already perfect entity such as myself
listen well fate i am your master now
what the hell it worked we're safe
so my love you too thank goodness
i was so worried
but how why
my magic is perfect there was no possible way i could have failed to seize control of that boy
how
so this is what you meant when you said that i could control destiny
i don't know too much yet about this power or how to use it but one thing's for certain
i can already tell it'll always side with me and those i hold dear
which means you and i don't have any ties
you
全て合算したら発散すれば愛だろう 恋だろう 名もは僕らが通り越して まだ名前などないその輝きを 己の中に見つけるんでしょ
天上天下 みな唯一がドックソング
ここはここにいるってことで あれでもないこれでもない今この瞬間ライフライフ
何処でいても変わらないでも Yeah yeah Yeah yeah yeah
不当たり前なの 何もなんでもないの
решって どこだってここは僕でいたいの
ウーウーウーウーウー
天上天下
Clover Clips
Vanessa Saw
Princess, please do me the honor of being my bride.
Yes, my prince. I'd be glad to marry you if you'll have me.
Indeed, my love. Why, you are as beautiful as the queen of witches who dwells within the forest.
Oh my goodness gracious me. You couldn't possibly mean such a thing.
The graceful and benevolent queen of witches is loved by all who know her in kingdoms near and far.
Of course I do. You are a most noble, kind, and elegant lady, just like the queen.
Oh, I'm so happy, my prince.
Let us embrace.
Ugh, sure is quiet around the old hideout when those knuckleheads are gone.
I mean, I'm glad I can take a dump in peace, but this is just too quiet.
I think I'm about ready for him to come back.
Black Clover, page 65. I'm home!
Oh, hey! There you are.